<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on BuddysCo - We help you search for study group. Find peers suited for you!</title><link>https://buddysco.com/categories/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on BuddysCo - We help you search for study group. Find peers suited for you!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 12:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://buddysco.com/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CAT Exam Success</title><link>https://buddysco.com/blog/somjit-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://buddysco.com/blog/somjit-blog/</guid><description>Achieving Your Goal of IIM Interview Calls
Written By: Somjit Banerjee
My Journey
I embarked on my CAT exam journey in 2021. Several months prior to November, around April, I committed to completing each topic on a monthly basis. Balancing my day job with night-time preparation posed a challenge, and staying motivated was no easy feat. Fortunately, I had unwavering support and encouragement from my family and friends throughout the process.</description></item><item><title>All about NEET(UG) Exam</title><link>https://buddysco.com/blog/neet-exam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://buddysco.com/blog/neet-exam/</guid><description>The National Eligibility Cum Entrance Test (NEET) UG formerly the All India Pre-Medical Test (AIPMT) is an all-India pre-medical entrance examination. NEET(UG) has been administered by the NTA since 2019. Before 2019, the test was conducted by the Central Board of Secondary Education (CBSE). It is the largest and most important medical entrance exam after the 12th. NEET is also the sole entrance test for admission to any medical course in India.</description></item><item><title>All about CAT Entrance Exam</title><link>https://buddysco.com/blog/cat-exam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://buddysco.com/blog/cat-exam/</guid><description>The Common Admission Test (CAT), which takes place every year under the supervision of the IIMs, is the primary entrance examination for prestigious business schools offering MBA programs. CAT 2024 will enable students to apply for admission to the IIMs and other leading institutes for the academic session of 2024-2026.
To be considered for MBA programs, students need to successfully pass this examination and meet the required minimum scores. Only those who meet the cut-off criteria will proceed to the subsequent selection rounds conducted by the institutions.</description></item><item><title>Mastering Competitive Exam Preparation: A Modern Guide</title><link>https://buddysco.com/blog/mastering-competitive-exam-prep/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://buddysco.com/blog/mastering-competitive-exam-prep/</guid><description>Introduction Competitive exams in India, such as the UPSC Civil Services, JEE for engineering, NEET for medical studies, and CAT for management, play a pivotal role in shaping the careers of countless aspirants. Effective preparation for these exams requires more than just hard work; it demands strategic planning, insightful approaches, and the right resources. This article provides a comprehensive guide on how to excel in competitive exams through individual efforts and the benefits of group study, enhancing your chances of success with a balanced, informed approach.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of Group Study</title><link>https://buddysco.com/blog/benefits-of-groupstudy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://buddysco.com/blog/benefits-of-groupstudy/</guid><description>Every person relies heavily on their education. One can only study one method. A lot of learners are perplexed about how they should structure their studies first for optimal comprehension and learning. Studying alone is the norm rather than the exception. If you want to study with others but your parents won't let you, you can show them the benefits of group study that we've listed below.
The Benefits of Studying in a Group Many people believe that studying in a group is a waste of time.</description></item></channel></rss>